♪I'll go with you to see your favorite flower in spring♪
♪سأذهب معك لرؤية زهرتك ​​المفضلة في الربيع♪
♪I'll treat you to your favorite ice cream in summer♪
♪ سأقدم لك الآيس كريم المفضل لديك في الصيف ♪
♪I'll be with you in the rain when you're sad in autumn♪
♪ سأكون معك تحت المطر عندما تكون حزيناً في الخريف ♪
♪I'll build a snowman for you in winter♪
♪ سأبني لك رجل ثلج في الشتاء ♪
♪Only you can have my romance♪
♪ أنت فقط من تستطيع الحصول على رومانسيتي ♪
♪Everyone else is secondary♪
♪ الجميع ثانوي ♪
♪I like your every smile and frown♪
♪ أحب كل ابتسامتك وعبوسك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪I want to take you to watch the stars♪
♪أريد أن آخذك لمشاهدة النجوم♪
♪Please♪
♪من فضلك♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪ دعني أعتني بك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪When it's cold, hide in my arms♪
♪ عندما يكون الجو بارداً، إختبئ بين ذراعي ♪
♪Drive all your sadness♪
♪ تخلص من كل حزنك ♪
♪Completely away♪
♪بعيد تمامًا♪
=Falling In Love With Me= =Episode 11=
=الوقوع في حبي= =الحلقة 11=
Are you really Lin Tongyu?
هل أنت حقا لين تونغيو؟
The one who writes songs
الشخص الذي يكتب الأغاني
for the excellent singers?
للمطربين الممتازين؟
I didn't mean to hide my identity from you.
لم أقصد إخفاء هويتي عنك.
I've kept it a secret
لقد أبقيت الأمر سرا
because I wanted to quietly do music.
لأنني أردت أن أعزف الموسيقى بهدوء.
So didn't you expose yourself due to me?
إذن ألم تعرضي نفسك بسببي؟
So you must work hard.
لذلك عليك أن تعمل بجد.
Don't let me down.
لا تخذلني.
But only three months left
ولكن لم يتبق سوى ثلاثة أشهر
before the competition.
قبل المنافسة.
Can I make it?
هل يمكنني تحقيق ذلك؟
You're actually very smart.
أنت في الواقع ذكي جداً.
It only took you a week
لقد استغرق الأمر منك أسبوعًا فقط
to get full marks in the music theory exam.
للحصول على العلامات الكاملة في امتحان نظرية الموسيقى.
And you're talented in songwriting.
وأنت موهوب في تأليف الأغاني.
I've listened to all your songs from the past three years.
لقد استمعت إلى جميع أغانيك من السنوات الثلاث الماضية.
Two of them are actually quite good.
اثنان منهم في الواقع جيدان جدًا.
Though your singing is very poor,
بالرغم من أن غنائك سيء للغاية،
that's not something that can't be changed.
هذا ليس شيئًا لا يمكن تغييره.
Really?
حقًا؟
Believe in yourself.
عليك ان تؤمن  بنفسك.
And trust me too.
وثق بي أيضًا.
But
لكن
weren't you always hating me before?
ألم تكن تكرهني دائمًا من قبل؟
Why are you helping me?
لماذا تساعدني؟
Because...
لأن...
Tong Erbao.
تونغ ارباو.
Mom.
أم.
You've been deceiving us for three years.
لقد خدعتنا لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
Three years.
ثلاث سنوات.
If it weren't for you showing your face on the live stream
لولا إظهار وجهك في البث المباشر
and being recognized by your cousin,
وأن يتم التعرف عليك من قبل ابن عمك،
we'd still be in the dark.
سنظل في الظلام.
We thought you were working in a publicly traded company.
اعتقدنا أنك تعمل في شركة مساهمة عامة.
Sit down.
اجلس.
Take deep breaths.
خذ نفسا عميقا.
Careful with your blood pressure.
حذرا مع ضغط الدم.
Don't argue in front of outsiders.
لا تجادل أمام الغرباء.
Erbao,
إرباو،
take us back to your room.
أعدنا إلى غرفتك.
What do you mean by my room?
ماذا تقصد بغرفتي؟
This is my house.
هذا منزلي.
The whole villa?
الفيلا كلها؟
You naughty girl.
يا ايتها البنت الشقية.
You bad girl.
أنت فتاة سيئة.
It's rented.
انها مستأجرة.
- Take it easy. - Oh, my God.
- خذها ببساطة.  - يا إلهي.
Auntie.
العمة.
Don't be so upset.
لا تنزعجي كثيرًا.
You shut up.
انت اسكت.
Pack your things and come home with me now.
احزمي أغراضك وعودي معي إلى المنزل الآن.
I'm not leaving.
أنا لا أغادر.
I still haven't learned how to sing.
مازلت لم أتعلم كيفية الغناء.
Sing. Sing.
يغني.  يغني.
Your life is nearly ruined by singing.
حياتك تكاد تدمر بالغناء.
Look at what people on the internet are saying about you.
انظر إلى ما يقوله الناس عنك على الإنترنت.
Erbao,
إرباو،
wake up.
استيقظ.
With your voice, you are simply not cut out for this.
بصوتك، أنت ببساطة غير مؤهل لهذا.
We're just ordinary people.
نحن مجرد أشخاص عاديين.
What's wrong with being ordinary?
ما العيب في أن تكون عادياً؟
Does being ordinary mean we can't pursue our dreams?
هل كوننا عاديين يعني أننا لا نستطيع تحقيق أحلامنا؟
Ordinary people are even more afraid of taking wrong paths.
بل إن الأشخاص العاديين يخافون أكثر من اتخاذ الطرق الخاطئة.
You're only in your twenties.
أنت فقط في العشرينات من عمرك.
When you're in your thirties,
عندما تكون في الثلاثينيات من عمرك،
without a good education background, a job, or a boyfriend,
بدون خلفية تعليمية جيدة، وظيفة، أو صديق،
you'll be doomed.
سوف يكون محكوم عليك.
Anyway, I'm not leaving.
على أية حال، أنا لن أغادر.
You...
أنت...
Uncle.
عم.
Auntie.
العمة.
Tong Yuxin is grown up now.
لقد كبر تونغ يوشين الآن.
She has her own opinions.
لديها آرائها الخاصة.
You can't force her into everything.
لا يمكنك إجبارها على كل شيء.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
He's here to teach me vocal music.
إنه هنا ليعلمني الموسيقى الصوتية
I think people like you who are into music
أعتقد أن الأشخاص مثلك مهتمون بالموسيقى
are all somewhat dubious.
كلها مشكوك فيها إلى حد ما.
Auntie,
العمة،
I'm a lecturer at the music academy.
أنا محاضر في أكاديمية الموسيقى.
Legitimate.
شرعي.
- A lecturer?
- محاضر؟  - محاضر؟
How old are you, young man?
كم عمرك أيها الشاب؟
Do you have a girlfriend?
هل لديك صديقة؟
Dad, Mom,
أبي أمي،
he's just here to teach me vocal music.
إنه هنا فقط ليعلمني الموسيقى الصوتية.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
He's not your boyfriend?
انه ليس صديقها الخاص بك؟
Then pack your things
ثم حزم الأشياء الخاصة بك
and come home with me now.
وتعال معي إلى المنزل الآن.
Dad, Mom,
أبي أمي،
you can't do this.
لا يمكنك فعل هذا.
Anyway, I will not leave with you.
على أية حال، لن أغادر معك.
Look at her.
انظر إليها.
She has been so spoiled.
لقد كانت مدللة جدا.
I told you
أخبرتك
we shouldn't let her work alone.
لا ينبغي لنا أن ندعها تعمل وحدها.
Alright, alright.
حسنا حسنا.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
I promise to listen to you from now on.
أعدك أن أستمع إليك من الآن فصاعدا.
Baby.
طفل.
I am aged and you still call me baby.
لقد كبرت ومازلت تناديني بالطفل.
You will always be my baby.
سوف تكون دائما طفلي.
Erbao can only be second.
Erbao يمكن أن يكون في المركز الثاني فقط.
Don't be angry, baby.
لا تغضب يا عزيزي.
Baby.
طفل.
Be good.
كن جيد.
Alright, baby.
الطفل بخير.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
Be good.
كن جيد.
Uncle. Auntie.
عم.  العمة.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
I'll leave now.
سأرحل الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
Dad. Mom.
أب.  أم.
I'll see him off.
سأودعه.
Tong Erbao.
تونغ ارباو.
After you come back.
بعد عودتك.
All right, don't be mad.
حسنًا، لا تغضب.
Don't be petty with her.
لا تكن تافهاً معها.
Calm down.
إهدئ.
Your fault.
خطأك.
She has grown up.
لقد كبرت.
Not three or five years old.
ليس ثلاث أو خمس سنوات.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Have they always been like this?
هل كانوا دائما هكذا؟
Don't wash our dirty linen in public.
لا تغسلوا بياضاتنا القذرة في الأماكن العامة.
Don't even mention it.
لا تذكر ذلك حتى.
I think
أظن
they are quite cute though.
هم لطيفون جدا بالرغم من ذلك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Where?
أين؟
Do you want to
هل تريد أن
go back with them?
العودة معهم؟
What else can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
Well,
حسنًا،
you want to elope with me?
هل تريد الهروب معي؟
Tong Yuxin,
تونغ يوكسين,
answer me a question.
أجب عني سؤالا.
Is music really your dream?
هل الموسيقى حقا حلمك؟
Do you want to stay here?
هل تريد البقاء هنا؟
I have a solution.
لدي حل.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Of course, it's
بالطبع، إنه كذلك
studying.
دراسة.
Studying?
دراسة؟
What time is it now?
كم الوقت الان؟
It's been six hours and she hasn't returned.
لقد مرت ست ساعات ولم تعد.
You've spoiled her.
لقد أفسدتها.
This time, I must take her back with me.
هذه المرة، يجب أن آخذها معي.
Don't rush.
لا تتعجل.
I promise I will listen to you from now on.
أعدك أنني سأستمع إليك من الآن فصاعدا.
You naughty boy.
يا الفتى المشاغب.
You guys.
يا رفاق.
It's already late.
انها بالفعل في وقت متأخر.
A man and a woman alone.
رجل وامرأة وحدهما.
Get off.
ترجل.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Dad, Mom.
أبي أمي.
We are studying.
نحن ندرس.
- Studying?
- دراسة؟  - دراسة؟
You met late in the night.
لقد التقيت في وقت متأخر من الليل.
Why did you study?
لماذا درست؟
Are you even a man?
هل أنت حتى رجل؟
Uncle, Auntie, I'm sorry.
عمي، عمتي، أنا آسف.
I asked Tong Yuxin here...
لقد سألت تونغ يوكسين هنا...
It is not Mr. Tang's fault.
إنه ليس خطأ السيد تانغ.
I just love studying.
أنا فقط أحب الدراسة.
What's wrong with learning to sing?
ما العيب في تعلم الغناء؟
No, it's me.
لا انها لي.
I wanted to teach Tong Yuxin.
كنت أرغب في تعليم تونغ يوكسين.
She's really talented
انها موهوبة حقا
and hardworking.
والعمل الدؤوب.
You should give her a chance.
يجب أن تعطيها فرصة.
Baby.
طفل.
What do you think we should do?
ماذا تعتقد أنه يجب علينا فعله؟
Tang.
تانغ.
You really do have faith in her,
أنت حقا تثق بها،
don't you?
أنت , لا؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll give you three days.
سأعطيك ثلاثة أيام.
(WeSing) Within three days.
(WeSing) في غضون ثلاثة أيام.
Erbao,
إرباو،
sing your "I Like You So Much"
غني أغنية "أنا معجب بك كثيرًا"
to SSS grade on the app.
إلى درجة SSS على التطبيق.
If you can't do it,
إذا كنت لا تستطيع أن تفعل ذلك،
go back home with me right away.
العودة إلى المنزل معي على الفور.
Deal.
اتفاق.
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪In the few weeks after breaking up♪
♪ في الأسابيع القليلة بعد الانفصال ♪
♪I restrain myself from missing you♪
♪ أنا أمنع نفسي من أن أفتقدك ♪
♪Like a chronic disease, it comes and goes♪
♪ مثل المرض المزمن، يأتي ويذهب ♪
♪Maybe I'm to blame for loving too deeply♪
♪ ربما أنا الملام على الحب العميق ♪
♪Will time heal the heartbreak♪
♪ هل الزمن سيشفي حسرة القلب ♪
♪Or will it make it more painful♪
♪ أم أنه سيجعل الأمر أكثر إيلاما ♪
♪Missing you is an incurable disease♪
♪ اشتياقك داء لا شفاء منه ♪
♪Yet now I think of you again♪
♪ والآن أفكر فيك مرة أخرى ♪
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪I am not afraid of lonely nights♪
♪أنا لا أخاف من الليالي المنعزلة♪
♪Everyone knows it is a lie♪
♪ الجميع يعلم أنها كذبة ♪
♪I don't want to bear the pain of missing again♪
♪ لا أريد أن أتحمل ألم الافتقاد مرة أخرى ♪
♪Can you please let me go♪
♪هل يمكنك أن تسمح لي بالذهاب ♪
♪The carriage of time won't stop♪
♪ لن تتوقف عربة الزمن ♪
♪I'm sorry. I can't be the person you're with for the rest of your life♪
♪ أنا آسف.  لا أستطيع أن أكون الشخص الذي أنت معه لبقية حياتك ♪